# ROBERT TRAN

DOB Address

12/09/1997 10 Solomon Crescent, Tingalpa

Phone Email Portfolio

0451129979 rtran.nvtt@gmail.com https://roberttran.netlify.app/



## **ABOUT ME**

I am a one year junior web developer with a passion in making front-end UI/UX design using different libraries such as React.js, Vue.js, Bootstrap, MUI, Three.js. I want to continue learning and growing my technical skill not only in front-end, but also back-end development with node.js, database management and web hosting.

# EDUCATION HISTORY

#### 2016-2019

# Bachelor of Information

#### **Technology**

Queensland University Of

Technology

- Basic and advanced methods of web development
- Mostly played developer role in teamwork.

#### 2020 - 2021

#### Professional Year at Navitas

- 3-month Internship at Centra Networks.
- Developed Professional Communication skills
- Developed the "Work hard Play hard" approach to life and work.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

6/2022 - 11/2022

#### Junior Web Developer, Pakko

- Maintain and update main website at https://Pakko.com.au/ with Wordpress.
- Design and create different web templates for internal usage.
- Create layout for IDP project at https://idp.pakko.com.au/
- Implement different UI/UX design/functionality for the IDP project, including: changing box color, control box with a 3d view cube, design options for customer when clicking on different surfaces
- Custom image editor for IDP with fabric.js. Apply the image saved in the image editor to the panel.
- Back-end development with node.js

#### 11/2020-2/2021

#### Web Developer/Designer Internship, Centra Networks

- Learn how to make and modify designs with photoshop.
- Design and implement service ticket template.
- Modify posters for CSAT (Centra Security Awareness Training) for internal use.
- Create a new catalogue design to introduce Centra Networks, with update of terms, services and conditions.
- Implement a referral page for the referral campaign.

## **PROJECTS**

Wordpress website: https://khoastories.com/

Wix style website: https://www.tranfoodphotography.com/

**University Music Website Project (Graduation Project)** 

- using HTML/CSS/JS and implement it to a local server for testing and data storaging.
- Designing the website and making the local server with XAMPP

#### **SKILLS**

## Web design and Implementation

https://roberttran.netlify.app/ https://idp.pakko.com.au/

Basic design skill with Figma, Photoshop

Keywords: HTML, CSS, Javascript, React/Nextjs, Vue/Nuxtjs, Bootstrap, MaterialUI, Photoshop, Wordpress, Illustration, Figma, GraphQL